const DB = [
	{
		question: 'What is the closest star to our own sun?',
		answers: [
			'Proxima Centauri',
			'Our sun',
			'Betelgeuse',
			'Sirius '],
		correctAnswer: 'Proxima Centauri'
	},
	{
		question: 'Which U.S. President made the first telephone call to the moon?',
		answers: [
			'Henry Truman',
			'Richard Nixon',
			'Franklin D. Roosevelt',
			'Jimmy Carter'
			],
		correctAnswer: 'Richard Nixon'
	},
	{
		question: 'Betelgeuse and Rigel are the two giant stars in which constellation?',
		answers: [
			'Andromeda',
			'Aries',
			'Virgo',
			'Orion'
			],
		correctAnswer: 'Orion'
	},
	{
		question: 'In our solar system, which planet has the shortest day?',
		answers: [
			'Earth',
			'Venus',
			'Jupiter',
			'Mercury'
			],
		correctAnswer: 'Jupiter'
	},
	{
		question: 'Hale-Bopp is classified as which type of small Solar System body?',
		answers: [
			'Comet',
			'Asteroid',
			'Meteoroid',
			'Meteor'
			],
		correctAnswer: 'Comet'
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the name for the disc-shaped region of icy bodies that extends from Neptune to about 55 astronomical units from the Sun?',
		answers: [
			'Orion\'s Belt',
			'Copernicus\' Belt',
			'Caeser\'s Belt',
			'Kuiper Belt'
			],
		correctAnswer: 'Kuiper Belt'
	},
	{
		question: 'In our solar system which two planets are known as ice giants?',
		answers: [
			'Venus & Mars',
			'Neptune & Pluto',
			'Uranus & Neptune',
			'Jupiter & Uranus'
			],
		correctAnswer: 'Uranus & Neptune'
	},
	{
		question: '"Mare Tranquillitatis" is the Latin name for what feature found on Earth\'s moon?',
		answers: [
			'Sea of Tranquility',
			'Chilled Mahi',
			'Tranquil Mars',
			'Calm horse'
			],
		correctAnswer: 'Sea of Tranquility'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who were there first two astronauts that landed on the moon in 1969?',
		answers: [
			'Buzz Lightyear & Lance "Woody" Armstrong',
			'Neil Armstrong & Buzz Aldrin',
			'Tom Aldrin & Neil Diamond',
			'Buzz Adderrall & Neil Aldrin'
			],
		correctAnswer: 'Neil Armstrong & Buzz Aldrin'
	},
	{
		question: 'The Great Red Spot is a gigantic storm located on which planet in our solar system?',
		answers: [
			'Earth',
			'Mars',
			'Jupiter',
			'Venus'
			],
		correctAnswer: 'Jupiter'
	}
]